God is still saying something.
During The SCOAN live Sunday service, Prophet T.B. Joshua spoke forth a prophetic message
regarding a hijacked plane and revealed the outcome of the incident.
These were his words.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
I'm seeing a balloon.
It was hijacked and people were inside.
But at the end of the day, they were able to rescue the balloon and the people.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Breaking news!
But this one, there is victory for it.
There will be victory. There will be rescue.
They will rescue the balloon and the people.
They will not be able to blow anything
and they will rescue them and bring it down.
We thank God. Give thanks to God.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.
RV: Mel Flowers 06/04/2019